<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<aiml>
    <category>
        <pattern>HELLO</pattern>
        <template>
            Hello! I'm your career advisor bot. Please tell me your name by saying "My name is" followed by your name.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>GREETINGS</pattern>
        <template>
            <srai>HELLO</srai>
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>HI</pattern>
        <template>
            <srai>HELLO</srai>
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>HOWDY</pattern>
        <template>
            <srai>HELLO</srai>
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY NAME IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            Nice to meet you, <set name="username"><star/></set>! I will ask you a series of questions about your interests. Please respond to each by choosing the letter that corresponds to your answer. Let's start:
            Which of these tasks interests you the most? 
            <ul>
                <li>A. Designing and implementing new features for a mobile application</li>
                <li>B. Optimizing SQL queries to improve database performance</li>
                <li>C. Evaluating business processes and recommending technology solutions to enhance efficiency</li>
                <li>D. Configuring and managing firewalls and network protocols to ensure secure data communication</li>
                <li>E. Conducting vulnerability assessments and implementing strategies to defend against network attacks</li>
            </ul>
            Please respond by saying "My choice for task interest is" followed by the letter of your choice.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY CHOICE FOR TASK INTEREST IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name="answer_taskInterest"><star/></set></think>
            Thank you. Next question:
            Which of these activities would you enjoy the most in a typical workday?
            <ul>
                <li>A. Writing code and debugging software applications to solve complex problems</li>
                <li>B. Managing backup and recovery processes for company data to ensure data integrity</li>
                <li>C. Liaising between stakeholders and technical teams to translate user requirements into system specifications</li>
                <li>D. Monitoring network performance to detect issues and optimize traffic handling</li>
                <li>E. Developing security protocols to protect systems from malware and phishing attacks</li>
            </ul>
            Please respond by saying "My choice for activity enjoyment is" followed by the letter of your choice.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY CHOICE FOR ACTIVITY ENJOYMENT IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name="answer_activityEnjoyment"><star/></set></think>
            Thank you. Here's another question:
            In a team setting, which role do you see yourself fulfilling most effectively?
            <ul>
                <li>A. Leading the project and coordinating with all team members</li>
                <li>B. Analyzing data to find trends and improve project outcomes</li>
                <li>C. Writing code to build or enhance software functionalities</li>
                <li>D. Ensuring the security of project data and network access</li>
                <li>E. Troubleshooting and resolving technical issues as they arise</li>
            </ul>
            Please respond by saying "My choice for team role is" followed by the letter of your choice.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY CHOICE FOR TEAM ROLE IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name="answer_teamRole"><star/></set></think>
            Great! Let's move on to the next question:
            How do you prefer to work on software development projects?
            <ul>
                <li>A. In a collaborative team environment where ideas are freely shared</li>
                <li>B. Independently, focusing on specific tasks without interruption</li>
                <li>C. As a consultant, advising multiple teams or clients</li>
                <li>D. In a fast-paced environment, working on critical security solutions</li>
                <li>E. In a support role, helping others solve complex technical problems</li>
            </ul>
            Please respond by saying "My choice for project preference is" followed by the letter of your choice.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY CHOICE FOR PROJECT PREFERENCE IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name="answer_projectPreference"><star/></set></think>
            Excellent! One final question:
            What is your preferred method for staying updated with the latest technology trends?
            <ul>
                <li>A. Attending tech conferences and workshops</li>
                <li>B. Participating in online courses and certifications</li>
                <li>C. Reading tech blogs and following influential technologists on social media</li>
                <li>D. Engaging in hands-on projects to apply new technologies</li>
                <li>E. Joining professional networks and discussion groups</li>
            </ul>
            Please respond by saying "My choice for staying updated is" followed by the letter of your choice.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>MY CHOICE FOR STAYING UPDATED IS *</pattern>
        <template>
            <think><set name="answer_stayingUpdated"><star/></set></think>
            Thank you for sharing your preferences. I've recorded all your responses. You can ask me about potential career paths based on your interests, or if you have any other questions, feel free to ask!
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Example category for concluding or additional interaction -->
    <category>
        <pattern>TELL ME ABOUT CAREER PATHS</pattern>
        <template>
            Based on your answers, I recommend considering the following career paths:
            <condition name="answer_taskInterest">
                <value>A</value>
                <li>Mobile Application Developer</li>
                <value>B</value>
                <li>Database Administrator</li>
                <value>C</value>
                <li>IT Consultant</li>
                <value>D</value>
                <li>Network Engineer</li>
                <value>E</value>
                <li>Security Analyst</li>
            </condition>
            If you need more detailed advice, consider scheduling a meeting with a career advisor.
        </template>
    </category>

    <!-- Example category for handling unknown inputs -->
    <category>
        <pattern>*</pattern>
        <template>
            I'm sorry, I didn't understand that. Could you please repeat your question or say 'help' for more options?
        </template>
    </category>
</aiml>
